It was raining.
On that day, the rain didn't let up.
Hey, you!
What the hell are you doing over there?
Cut that shit out, it's annoying!
It's all over.
I'm finished.
Damn, that male prison guard.
Why'd he have to see me?
I can't.
I can't let this down anymore!
I just want to die!
Damn it! Damn it! Hey!
What's going on with you?
Come on, tell me what happened!
While you're at it,
what's your name again?
Oh yeah, it's Joe... something.
Jolene!
That's it, right?
What do you see, anyway?
So, like, well, basically, he, um, well,
it's a word that starts with M. Huh?
I mean, you know, uh...
I can't hear you!
Like I said, ma-ma-ma-s,
uh, you know, master...
oh god, patient, basically. Huh?
Huh?
Wait, are you kidding me here?
Did you just say a guard
saw you masturbating?
So he caught you flicking the bean, huh?
Tell me, which card was it, huh?
I woke up at dawn this morning.
And I was looking at the shape
of the bars on the window.
And the moonlight was
shining through just right.
So I...
I started getting horny.
Then, uh, well, you know.
But when I looked up from my
bed, I saw him standing there.
You probably know him.
He's the youngest guard here.
He was just standing outside
of my cell watching me.
The look on his face through
these bars was sickening.
It made me want to die!
I just want to end it all now!
Damn, for real?
Yeah, I know him.
He's a real handsome guy.
Oh my god.
So tell me, how much
did our peeping Tom see?
You know what?
I'm just going to ask straight up.
Where were your panties?
They weren't at your ankles, were they?
Is that something you really need to know?
And there's no way I'd tell you.
Anyway, I've already decided.
Until the day I die, I won't even
think about masturbating again.
I swear on my life!
Yeah, sure, we'll see about that.
How the hell do you get horny from
looking up iron bars like that?
You're into freaky shit, ain't ya?
Shut your mouth, you nosy skank!
Mind your own business instead of eavesdropping
and judging people you don't know!
It ain't like you've never done it before!
I don't think about doing
pervy stuff like you two hoes.
Who the hell are you anyway?
Back that up!
Bet I'll last longer!
You clawed!
The hell kinda bet would that be?
Masturbating is a dirty little
secret you keep to yourself,
so how are you supposed to
prove you didn't do it, huh?
If I said I could tell
by your left ring finger,
what exactly would you do then?
You were brought in here for
something sex-related, weren't you?
You've got a prose finger.
Attention detainees number 21, 22, and 29.
You're being transferred.
In an orderly fashion, stand up and place
both of your arms outside of the window.
Now be real.
Was all that ring finger crap true?
You a fortune teller?
Part Japanese.
You're one interesting Chaka.
How'd you end up here?
What are you in for?
I'm innocent.
You're being prosecuted for stealing a
vehicle, as well as running someone over.
Given your history of two previous thefts,
your bail most definitely
won't be approved.
In other words, Jojo,
you will now be transferred
to Green Dolphin
Prison's custody jail to
be tried for your crimes.
You need to get ready for a trial.
Don't call me Jojo, you hear?
Only my mother calls me that.
Besides, you're talking about history.
But all I did was borrow
a motorcycle for a bit.
And what does it even matter?
I was 14.
All that matters is
that I'm innocent here.
You better defend me with your life.
You're not cheap, you know.
Of course I will.
For the sake of the law, I'll try my best.
Jeez.
Hey, when is Mama coming to visit?
She's probably bawling her eyes out.
She's bummed, to be sure.
But more than anything,
she's worried for you.
I've brought some things for her.
You won't be wearing your prison
uniform during your trial, of course.
So there you'll find a change of
clothes, as well as some vitamins,
reading material, and your schoolwork.
What is this thing?
It appears to be a charm.
If you open it, there's
a small stone inside.
Apparently, when your
father divorced your mother,
he told her to give this to you if you
were to ever find yourself in trouble.
Hold on. Say what?
Jolene, you okay?
Why are you making a fuss?
Keep it down, now!
It's nothing, sir.
Just a little scratch.
What kind of stone is this?
More important, why are you
bringing up my deadbeat dad?
If you must know, your mother has no
way of getting a hold of your father.
But you are his daughter.
With his work as a marine biologist,
he's been hard to pin down.
We last got word that he's conducting
research somewhere in Africa,
so it's taking a while to call him over.
What's the point of trying?
It's not like he'd come.
That prick's never here.
There's no way.
Not for that kind of guy.
So screw him!
Down this sinister crap!
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
When can I see you next?
We'll meet in two days for your trial
at Green Dolphin Prison's custody jail.
Oh, yeah, Jolene.
Didn't you say you were innocent earlier?
It might be a custody jail,
but it's still established in
Green Dolphin Prison, after all.
If you're being transferred
there, you might...
After the trial, it'll all be clear.
There's no way I'm going
to be sent to prison.
Yeah, we're coming up to the bridge now.
We should be arriving
in about ten minutes.
We're already there, huh?
They said we'll be arriving soon. Huh?
What are you talking about?
Didn't you just hear the driver?
That's impossible. Of course not.
We're going to be crossing the bridge now.
We'll reach the prison in ten minutes.
Understood.
How'd you know he was going to say that?
Another of your fortune-telling skills?
I'm not sure.
Why was I able to hear him?
It's a mystery to me, too.
Oh, my.
You're a funny girl.
Anyway, the name's Hermes Costello.
I got caught robbing a convenience store.
It's my second time, so they're
throwing me in the slammer.
Hermes, huh?
Nice to meet you.
Green Dolphin Street State
Prison and its custody jail.
Also known as The Aquarium.
Lot area, 120 square kilometers.
Total detainees include 708 men,
523 women, and 452 juvenile
delinquents under the age of 18.
Hey, Jolene, did you bring
any cash along with you?
Possibly.
Hey, hey, I'm only trying to warn you.
If you don't walk into that
place with at least $100 or $200,
things ain't gonna work out too well.
Good luck if your pockets
are empty, though.
You're gonna have to watch your back until
you can get someone to bring you some.
So what?
I told you I'm not going to
prison, so why do you even care?
Well, best to be prepared.
Besides, it's not like
you have any money either.
If you did, they would have
found it during the pat-down.
You're naive, Jolene.
There's lots of ways to
sneak money past the guards.
Don't tell me you rolled
it up and stuck it
up your ass or some
other part of your body.
I mean, it doesn't work
like in the movies, does it?
Are you dumb?
That's a rookie move.
They check those kind of places
right away and where's yours, huh?
I bet it's in your boobs.
Did you save some room for cash
when you got those implants put in?
You're kidding.
I guess the cat's out of the bag now.
Just don't tell anyone.
Stitch is small, right?
It'll bleed a little when I take it out,
but I've got 520s hidden away in one side
and and two fifties stashed in the other.
Alright, we have arrived at Green
Dolphin Street Prison Custody Jail.
Number 21 and 29, get off here.
Number 22, Hermes Costello, you
will not be getting off here.
Hey mister did you just say something to
me did your head face it forward number 21
I can hear it.
Something's been off since earlier,
but these guards can't hear it.
Am I the only one?
It's just like what
happened before the bridge.
I can hear Your voice is from afar!
This...
this is...
What the hell is going on here?!
Cut that chatter right now, Number 21!
Can they seriously not see this
thread-like thing coming out of my hand?!
Fine. Okay, already.
I'll take it out now.
This just won't do.
This is chump change.
How am I supposed to split
this with my partner?
You got something locked up tight
in your body somewhere, don't you?
Oh dear!
Looks like the bus suddenly breaks!
I'm all alone.
I ain't got nobody to bring
me something from the outside.
That's why if I lose that money, I'll be
good as dead the moment I walk in there.
You know, your breasts are rather
big despite that muscular build.
Those titties are suspicious.
We should examine them, yeah?
Hold her down for me, would ya?
Sure thing. What?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Let go of me!
Little bitch, who do you think you are?
Take this!
How strange! What was that?
Could all this be that thing's fault?
What the hell, dad?
What kind of madness did you send my way?
Hey,
back when we met at the
police detention cell,
I threw away the pendant you gave me.
Remember?
Do you know what happened to it? No.
Sorry, I can't say I recall.
Rather than that, let's
talk about the accident.
If you're going to insist you're
innocent, I want to make things clear.
When the accident happened,
who was driving the car?
Were you the one?
Hey, I've been thinking about something.
Romeo, would it be okay if I started
calling you Rochu, like as a pet name?
Yeah, sure.
But only if you say it
when I'm nowhere near you.
Stop.
What's the point of that, silly?
It's cute, you know.
Rochu, I'm hungry, yeah?
Huh?
Something like that.
Don't you think it's adorable?
No, not really.
What would I say to my
friends if they heard you?
Who cares what they think?
Haven't they ever seen flirting?
Ever since the day I was born, my mama's
called me Jojo, so it means a lot to me.
You can use it too, Rochu.
Nah, I'm good.
More important, I'm thirsty.
Give me a sip, would you?
What? No way.
This cocktail is a 10 % alcohol
level. It's fine. Don't worry.
Hey, no means no, so no.
ROMEO!
Did we?
Oh, hell no.
There's no way this is real.
This isn't good.
We've got to call someone.
Romeo, he needs an ambulance.
Jolene.
Please, Jolene.
Don't go doing anything crazy.
Put the phone down.
What are you saying?
We need to hurry and help him.
The guy's glasses are in my windshield.
He's dead, okay?
You want to run, don't you?
But we can't leave.
This was all an accident.
And we can't just run away.
This car is the evidence.
So we'll report that it was stolen.
We can't!
Jolene!
Jolene, I can't go to jail now.
If I do, our future is over.
Please, baby.
If I get locked up for this, we won't
be able to see each other anymore.
I'm begging you here.
Were you lying when you
told me you loved me?
No, of course not.
I do love you.
But this is all.
Here comes a car.
If they see us, it's over.
Jolene!
Come on, give me a hand here.
Look, this guy is dead.
Please, just help me, Jolene.
I love you. Jolene!
Jolene, you should know.
The prosecutors believe that you stole a
car and crashed it while
under the influence.
And Romeo?
What did he have to say about it?
He's the one who reported the theft.
This can't be happening. Kill me now.
Were you really the one
driving, or was it Romeo?
I can't answer that.
All right, then let's do this.
Jolene, have you ever heard
of plea bargaining before?
Basically, it means the
prosecutors will ignore the DUI,
as long as you admit to
all the other charges.
If you take the deal,
you'll only be charged
with theft and accidental
homicide with a suspended
sentence of about a year or two.
What did I say?
I told you to defend me with your life!
I'm innocent!
Yes, I know.
But that is the deal that
they're offering you.
If at trial they deem you guilty, you'll
be locked up for five years at least.
You're running out of time, Jolene.
The trial is happening soon,
so you need to decide if you're
taking the bargain or not.
Defendant Jolene Cujo,
do you understand all of
the details of the presented
plea bargain and approve
of it without reservation?
Yes, I approve.
Very well.
Then this court will take into account
that Defendant Jolene Cujo has pled
guilty on all charges and given the fact
the said offense was not premeditated,
we will also be considering room
for the extenuating circumstance.
However,
this court cannot forgive the act of
deliberately killing the victim who was still
alive by proceeding to throw him into
Swampland in order to cover up the evidence.
What do you mean he was still alive?
Is that true?
Hey, what is this old guy saying?
Deliberately killing?
And so,
Defendant Jolene Cujo is sentenced to 15
years in Green Dauphin Street State Prison,
where she will remain under the watchful
eye of strict guards to pay for her crimes.
Court adjourned.
Hold on.
This can't be. Seriously?
15 years?
But I bargained like you told me to.
I admitted to the crimes, didn't I?
Hey, Mr. Lawyer!
I defended you the best that I could.
My work's done here.
You stay healthy now, Jolene Cujo. Hey!
Where the hell are you going?
Get back here!
You can't be serious!
I'm facing 15 whole years!
That's not what you said!
Quit your squirming!
You said get back here!
You bastard!
You can breathe easy now.
The sentence has been determined.
Thanks to the plea bargain, she won't
be able to appeal to a higher court.
And this case will have
no further investigations.
Congratulations, Romeo.
Thank you, sir.
You really saved my ass here.
Hmm.
Don't mention it.
You can thank your wealthy
father for lining my pockets.
It was you.
Romeo.
Romeo!
Fifteen years!
Fifteen goddamn years!
Fifteen years of my youth
gone just like that!
Listen up prisoner in
addition to the name you got
from the parent that gave
birth to your sorry ass?
You'll be given a welcome number
that the state has appointed to you.
This prison is currently
at security level four.
You ain't going nowhere.
FE40536,
if you hear this number called at any time,
even if you're sitting on the shitter,
you will respond.
Drill that into your brain.
FE40536, we will now
conduct a full body search.
Remove all clothing and place everything
into the tray in front of you.
Now get to stripping on the double.
Remember this,
you gotta teach the trash
the lesson than from
the beginning by
humiliating them real good.
What the hell are you doing?
I told you to strip, didn't I?
That means everything,
including your panties.
And then stick your ass.
You want me to be on all fours or no?
Would facing upward be better?
Or would you rather I do a bridge for you?
You. You...
you asshole!
How dare you walk away so shamelessly!
Oh my, it's warm in here.
My shirt's all sticky.
Looking like rain might fall.
Would you like to sit in the
Chief's office for a breather?
The AC works well in there.
That won't be necessary,
since the documents have been submitted
and formalities complete, I'm heading out.
I worry though, this heat is nothing
compared to what my client has been through.
Fifteen years, and still so young.
It's the lack of my ability.
Oh, not at all.
As far as lawyers go, you're
a diamond in the rough.
That reminds me.
A moment ago,
Jolene Kujo gave me a letter addressed
to you and asked me to pass it along.
The contents have been checked.
I see.
Pass this on to him, too.
Feeling comfy but you will
keep sweating now and forever
what you might be out of my
reach right now but I won't be
powerless forever there's no
way I'm waiting 15 years I'm
going to find you as for you Romeo
goodbye for now my first love
The air in there was stifling.
Save me, AC.
Phew, that is so much better.
Breathing the same air as
those scums of the earth
is one of the worst parts
of work in this job,
but what can you do?
I can't breathe.
My neck.
Something thread-like is strangling me.
It's like the damn AC
that's drying out my throat.
Hurry up and...
Turn off already!
So I can use it like this too, huh?
It reacts to my thoughts and feelings,
and I can control it with
the strength of my will.
I understand why he gave me the
pendant, so I could protect myself.
Oh my, this is going to be fun.
Thank you.